Oversize
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Oversize
2.1.1.2.12
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1330
- Oversize, 2.1.1.2.12
  - Ancestors [split glass plate negative], undated; 1; 8x10 (Box 1330)
  - Ancestors [split glass plate negative], undated; 2; 8x10 (Box 1330)
  - Ancestors [split glass plate negative], undated; 3; 8x10 (Box 1330)
  - Isaac’s Tomb, Abraham’s Tomb, Mayor of Jerusalem and two British soldiers at surrender of Jerusalem [split glass plate negative], 1918; 4; 2-281 2-282 2-283; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1330)
  - View from airplane of Port Said (aerial view), Sudan sandstorm [split glass plate negative], 1918; 5; 3-104 3-105; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1330)
  - Lowell Thomas and T. E. Lawrence standing in front of tent, 1918; 6; 4-3; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1330)
  - Lowell Thomas with motion picture camera in airplane before taking off for a flight from Egypt to Jerusalem, 1918; 7; 4-17; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1330)
  - Two airplanes in clouds, one plane in cloud, squadron on ground, 1918; 8; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1330)
  - Linton Wells (copy made for Lowell Thomas), 1925 July 1; 9; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1330)
  - Map of Near East, Petra indicated with bright red star, 1920; 10; 1-206; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1330)
  - Auda Abu Tayi, center, and two brothers, 1918; 11; 1-71; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1330)